<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on devICT</title>
    <link>http://devict.org/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on devICT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 18:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://devict.org/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-09-19 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-09-19/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  None   Guests  None   III. Approval of Minutes IV. Old Business a. Leadership info is on website. b. Sandip is looking into insurance. c. Bank account d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-08-08 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-08-08/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order at 6:06 by Casey Woolfolk
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  None   Guests  None   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-07-18 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-07-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-07-18/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order by Casey Woolfolk at 6:05 PM.
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  Jacob Walker Julia Winegeart Casey Woolfolk Sandip Southekal  Absent  Seth Etter   Guests  None   III. Approval of Agenda IV. New Business a. Appoint a Temporary Chair and Secretary  Motion: I move that Casey Woolfolk be appointed as temporary chair for this meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>