<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on devICT</title>
    <link>http://devict.org/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on devICT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 12:10:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://devict.org/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-09-17 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 12:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-09-17/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order at 12:12 by Jacob Walker
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  Secretary - Richard Sharp   Guests  Jacob Hobbie Edward Jacobs Nic Wentling George Shaw Brian Pirot Michael Dorian Michael Campbell Chris Lofland Kevin Elledge Tonya Riepe Michael Neth Jim Rice Brian Foster Jake Suellentrop   III.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-08-01 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-08-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 19:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-08-01/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  Guests  III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.  By: Second: Result:   IV. Financial Report Casey to provide a status update for the internal accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-06-06 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-06-06/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order at 19:20.
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  Secretary - Richard Sharp   Guests  Jacob Hobbie Ed Mangimelli George Shaw   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019-01-09 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-01-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2019-01-09/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal  Absent  Director - Seth Etter   Guests  None   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.  By: Jacob Walker Second: Julia Winegeart Result: Approved   IV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-12-05 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-12-05/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal  Absent  Secretary - Richard Sharp Director - Seth Etter   Guests  Jim Rice   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.  By: Casey Woolfolk Second: Jacob Walker Result: Approved   IV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-11-01 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-11-01/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk  Absent  Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter   Guests  Michael Campbell   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.  By: Casey Woolfolk Second: Jacob Walker Result: Approved   IV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-09-19 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-09-19/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order  Meetings began at 6:08pm CST  II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  None   Guests  None   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-08-08 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-08-08/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order at 6:06 by Casey Woolfolk
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  President - Jacob Walker Vice President - Julia Winegeart Secretary - Richard Sharp Treasurer - Casey Woolfolk Director - Sandip Southekal Director - Seth Etter  Absent  None   Guests  None   III. Approval of Minutes  Motion: I move to accept the minutes from our prior meeting as presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018-07-18 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-07-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devict.org/meetings/2018-07-18/</guid>
      <description>I. Call to Order Called to order by Casey Woolfolk at 6:05 PM.
II. Roll Call  Board Members  Present  Jacob Walker Julia Winegeart Casey Woolfolk Sandip Southekal  Absent  Seth Etter   Guests  None   III. Approval of Agenda IV. New Business a. Appoint a Temporary Chair and Secretary  Motion: I move that Casey Woolfolk be appointed as temporary chair for this meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>